# ANANDA KRISHNAN R

# **UI** Designer

95514 07826

- No. 2/76, Pachaiyamman Kovil, Amarambedu, Kundrathur, Chennai 600069.
- design2anand@gmail.com Be https://www.behance.net/chottuji

## **ABOUT ME**

A position where my vision is to bring forth the best of my creative & management skills, and Wealth of knowledge thus making optimum contribution to mutual growth. Designer with 4 years of experience innovative approach to idea and concept development good focus communication, clear understanding of modern technologies and best design practices.

## **EDUCATION**

2014 - 2017

Diploma in Mechanical Engineering AMK Technological Polytechnic college

2019 - 2020

**Graphic Desiging in MAAC Academy Cinematics** 

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2020 - 2021

#### **Tuhur Creative Studio**

**UI** Designer

- Illustrated page design concepts by blending arrangements, Style and better elementic to meet predetermined preferences.
- Websites and Mobile Applications, Branding design, Digital Marketing, Social media post.

2017 - 2019

#### **Rejoice Digital**

**Graphic Designer** 

- Worked with clients to gather and define the requirements with their need and satisfaction.
- Created corporate promotional design, logos, Pamphlet & brouchers, business cards, Banner, Social media post.

#### **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

Adobe Photoshop Adobe XD CSS 3 Indesign

Adobe Illustrator Figma HTML 5 Coreldraw